<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<paranorm>
    <navigation>
		<main id="home">Home</main>
		<main id="house">Haunted House</main>
		<main id="entities">Entities</main>
		<main id="phenomena">Phenomena</main>
	</navigation>
	<phenomena id = "1">
	<name> Clocks of Sicily </name>
	<info>
	<place> Sicily, Italy </place>
	<history>  In Catania, 
	suddenly all the electrical clocks have been spinning ahead by 6-20 minutes. 
	It has been a persistent problem. 
	A technological group was called in to investigate. 
	In Canneto di Caronia, they experienced spontaneous combustion of 
	electrical appliances to the extent that even unplugged fires would break out. 
	It began in January 2004  </history>
	</info>
	</phenomena>	
		
	

	<phenomena id = "2">
	<name> Black eyed people </name>
	<info>
	<place> USA </place>
	<history> tt started in 1998 when journalist Brian Bethel 
	gave an account of being approached by two boys as he entered his car. 
	The boys allegedly asked him for a lift. 
	He described experiencing a sudden feeling of fear and panic,
	while at the same time having an overwhelming urge to open the door 
	for the boys. He then noticed their eyes ֠they were entirely coal black,
	with no whites visible. 
	Bethel drove away in fear even as the teens became more insistent. </history>
	</info>
	</phenomena>	
	
	<phenomena id = "2">
	<name> Fisher's Ghost </name>
	<info>
	<place> Australia </place>
	<history> On a calm June evening in 1826, 
	Fisher left his house in Campbelltown to run some errands, 
	never to return.  
	Four months after Fisher vanished,
	a local resident stumbled into a Campbelltown hotel, 
	pale and shaken to his very bones. He told the assorted 
	audience that he had just encountered the ghost of Frederick Fisher. 
	The spectral farmer had been sitting on a fence by the road, pointing
	with his finger at a paddock near the river that ran nearby. 
	Then, the startled man watched the apparition fade away in front 
	of his eyes. The man who had seen the ghost was a wealthy and
	well-respected member of the community, so the police decided 
	to investigate the paddock the ghost had pointed at. To their shock,
	they found the body of Frederick Fisher, dead and hidden from view.
	His murderer was soon found to be one George Worrall, 
	Fisherӳ neighbor and friend who had been taking care of his legal matters 
	in the past. Worrall had already raised some eyebrows
	after Fisherӳ disappearance, as he told everyone that 
	Fisher had sailed to England and soon started selling
	the poor farmerӳ belongings. The emergence of the body 
	soon caused Worrall to confess, and Fisher could finally 
	rest in peace. </history>
	</info>
	</phenomena>	
		
	<phenomena id = "4">
	<name> Hawkesbury mosnter</name>
	<info>
	<place> Australia </place>
	<history> Hawkesbury River, a wide and murky New South Wales estuary,
	is Australiaӳ answer to Loch Ness. According to 
	cryptozoology enthusiasts and local historians alike, 
	there is some evidence that Hawkesbury is inhabited by one or more giant, 
	water-dwelling monsters. 
	Eyewitnesses have reported these creatures to be as long as 24 meters 
	(79 ft) and, much like ԎessieԠof Loch Ness, 
	the monster is said to resemble an aquatic dinosaur, 
	most likely a plesiosaur. 
	Although the Hawkesbury River monster has reportedly 
	been glimpsed by the locals at least since the 1960s 
	(and possibly even longer, as Aboriginal legends place 
	similar creatures in the area), no one has ever been able 
	to take a photograph of one. If the monster is indeed real,
	this may change in the future: A particularly enthusiastic 
	monster hunter called Rex Gilroy is currently on a quest to 
	catch the creature on film. </history>
	</info>
	</phenomena>	
	

</paranorm>